[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If my opponent in gin rummy has picked up the 8 of diamonds, and I know nothing else about my opponents hand, which of the following cards should I discard?", "correct_answer": "7 of spades", "incorrect_answers": ["8 of spades", "9 of diamonds", "10 of diamonds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which city used to be called Lutetia?", "correct_answer": "Paris", "incorrect_answers": ["Leiden", "Madrid", "London"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This person was recognized as the first billionaire.", "correct_answer": "John D. Rockefeller", "incorrect_answers": ["Hassan Ibn Ganeff", "Andrew Carnegie", "Bill Gates"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1927 Austrian baker and confectioner, Eduard Haas invented what?", "correct_answer": "PEZ candy", "incorrect_answers": ["The electric mixer", "AM radio", "The CAT scan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Man bought an old motorcycle only to discover that it was once owned by Elvis Presley.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Lucky Number Slevin Morgan Freeman plays the Rabbi.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average lifespan of a nautilus?", "correct_answer": "20 years", "incorrect_answers": ["10 years", "2 years", "40 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Chief of Police Martin Brody in the classic movie Jaws?", "correct_answer": "Roy Scheider", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Shaw", "Justin McAllister", "Richard Dreyfuss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sean Connery, George Lazenby, Roger Moore, Timothy Dalton and Pierce Brosnan have all played the role of a fictional British spy. Who was that character?", "correct_answer": "James Bond", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnny English", "Jim Malone", "Eliot Ness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gemologists use eleven grades to define clarity. This grade means there are no inclusions or surface blemishes under 10x magnification.", "correct_answer": "FL (Flawless)", "incorrect_answers": ["IF (Internally Flawless)", "I1 (Imperfect  Level 1)", "VS1 / VS2 (Very Slightly Included)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Chihuahua is the smallest dog breed in the world.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What temperature, in degrees Celsius, is Absolute Zero?", "correct_answer": "-273", "incorrect_answers": ["-32", "-135", "-356"]}]